{
    "question": "Arti what happened to the writers dad when he rode an elephant?",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>artinya: apa yang terjadi pada ayahnya penulis ketika dia menunggang gajah?</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>indonesia translation : apa yang terjadi kepada ayah penulis saat dia menaiki gajah?</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan: hope you find this helpful^\u2022^</p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "complete-the-sentences-use-the-present-continuous-from-of-the-the-417",
            "question": "Complete the sentences use the present continuous from of the the brackets    4. a. my uncle.....( wash ) his car. b.they ..... (listen) to the rock music\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>4. A. My uncle is washing his car. </p><p>B.  They are listening to the rock music. </p><p></p><p>Semoga membantu ^_^</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p> </p><p>a.My uncle washed his car.</p><p>b.They listen to rock music.</p><p> </p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "eyelash-is-to-apa-artinya-173",
            "question": "Eyelash is to apa artinya\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Bulu mata berfungsi untuk.....</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Eyelash is to</p><p>Bulu mata berfungsi untuk....</p><p></p><p>artian untuk kata tersebut bisa berubah tergantung topik pembicaraan</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "two-children-didnt-come-tofriends-birthday-party-950",
            "question": "Two children didn't come to...friend's birthday party",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>dua anak-anak tidak datang ke...pesta ulang tahun teman</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalau salah..kamu menanyakan arti kan? :v</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "38-a-part-of-songs-which-tells-the-story-is-called-a-chorus-b-246",
            "question": "38. A part of songs which tells the story is called..    A. Chorus\r\nB. Pre-chorus\r\nC. Verse\r\nD. Coda\r\n\r\n39. A part of songs which is also called as tail is.. \r\nA. Chorus\r\nB. Pre-chorus\r\nC. Verse\r\nD. Coda\r\n\r\n40.A part songs which usually repeated in a song is... \r\nA. Chorus\r\nB. Pre-chorus\r\nC. Verse\r\nD. Coda\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nBantu jawab\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>38.C. Verse</p><p>Penjelasan=<u>A\u00a0verse\u00a0is a repeated section of a\u00a0song\u00a0that typically features a new set of lyrics on each repetition. ... And while choruses typically contain a\u00a0song&#039;s\u00a0signature\u00a0musical\u00a0motif, the\u00a0music\u00a0of a\u00a0verse\u00a0is often written to complement the chorus\u00a0music.</u></p><p></p><p><u>3</u><u>9</u><u>.</u><u>D</u><u>.</u><u> </u><u>C</u><u>o</u><u>d</u><u>a</u></p><p><u>p</u><u>e</u><u>n</u><u>j</u><u>e</u><u>l</u><u>a</u><u>s</u><u>a</u><u>n</u><u>=</u><u>Coda is an Italian word for \"tail,\" it is the additional lines of a\u00a0song\u00a0which brings it to a close. The coda is an optional addition to a\u00a0song.</u></p><p></p><p><u>4</u><u>0</u><u>.</u><u>A</u><u>.</u><u> </u><u>C</u><u>h</u><u>o</u><u>r</u><u>u</u><u>s</u></p><p><u>p</u><u>e</u><u>n</u><u>j</u><u>e</u><u>l</u><u>a</u><u>s</u><u>a</u><u>n</u><u>=</u><u>When a distinction is made, the chorus is\u00a0the part\u00a0that contains the hook or the \"main idea\" of a\u00a0song&#039;s\u00a0lyrics and\u00a0music, and there is rarely variation from one\u00a0repetition\u00a0of the chorus to the next</u></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "rearrange-the-sentences-become-a-good-dialog-a-1-5-3-4-2-243",
            "question": "Rearrange the sentences become a good dialog.\u00a0*    \ufffc\r\n\r\nA. 1-5-3-4-2\r\n\r\nB. 2-5-3-4-1\r\n\r\nC. 2-4-1-5-3\r\n\r\nD. 1-5-2-4-3\r\n\r\nsecepatnya \r\n\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>2-4-1-5-3</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>2. Edo : Have you seen real monkey,Udin? i mean not on tv or in a magazine?</p><p>4. Udin : Yes,I have.</p><p>1. Edo : What are they like?</p><p>5. Udin : They&#039;re very friendly and playful.</p><p>3. Edo : Wow! That&#039;s interesting because as far as i know, not all monkeys are friendly. I want to see one too.</p><p></p><p>hope you find this helpful ^\u2022^</p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "please-arrange-these-words-1-wendy-books-super-comic-lo-283",
            "question": "Please arrange these words:    1. wendy - books - super - comic - loves - heroes. - about\r\n ____________________________________________\r\n 2.tiara - sand - make - wich. - know - how to\r\n ____________________________________________\r\n\r\n tolong yaa kakak yang cantiiiik dan abang abang",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. wendy - loves, - comic - books - about - super - heroes</p><p>2. tiara - know - how to - make - sand - wich</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>smoga membantu\u25c9\u203f\u25c9</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. wendy loves comic books about super heroes</p><p>2. Tiara know how to make sandwich</p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "you-have-asking-your-family-member-about-their-habit-533",
            "question": "You have asking your family member about their habit\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>kamu telah menanyakan ke keluargamu tentang hobi mereka</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "the-sentences-below-in-indirect-speechanisa-said-i-will-have-cal-341",
            "question": "The sentences below in indirect speech,anisa said i will have called my mother",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>anisa said that she will has called her mother</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "text-for-questions-number-21-23-i-am-an-smp-student-my-name-i-419",
            "question": "Text for questions number 21 - 23.    I am an SMP student. My name is Randi. I have\r\none sister and two brothers. My sister's name is Tasya\r\nand my brothers' names are Bimo and Zaky. My father's\r\nname is Bambang and my mother's name is Alya. I live\r\nwith my family at 7 Batu Sangkar Street.\r\nI am twelve years old. Tasya is ten years old. Bimo\r\nis six years old. Zaky is three years old. My father is\r\nfourty three and my mother is fourty. We are good\r\nfamily\r\n21. Randi's sister is ..... years old.\r\nb. 6\r\na. 3\r\nc. 10\r\nd. 12\r\nUt?\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>21. C. 10 years old </p><p>semoga membantu :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>21. Randy&#039;s sister is..... years old</p><p>c.10</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p> Semoga membantu!</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "thankyou-momy-you-for-risking-your-life-your-useless-doughter-thi-535",
            "question": "Thankyou momy you for risking your life your useless doughter this love",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p> Terima kasih ibu, kau telah mempertaruhkan nyawamu demi cintamu yang tak berguna ini</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}